I left without
a bit
of much direction
and ended up
cycling the country
and it was
a very intense
and spiritual journey
, where I
felt like, "Oh,
websites, that's not
very purposeful. What,
why am I
making websites? I
wanna, like, change
the world and
save peoples' lives."
but then I
went overseas for
a little bit,
a bit
after that,
and I was
like, wait a
second, people are
struggling to make
ends meet, not
following their exact
purpose in life
or their dream
and they're
just battling
to survive. Like,
surely, I can
make websites that
I'm good at,
and enjoy
for a
while and maybe
some of that
bigger impact stuff,
bigger picture stuff
can come later.
so that's,
yeah, so there
was about a
year of limbo
there and then
I came back
to building websites
and projects started
picking up better.
There were, there
were moments of,
you know, "How
am I gonna
pay rent this
week?" through that
period, for sure.
but now in
these past maybe
six months or
so, things have
been fairly steady,
which has been
awesome, and actually
in the past
two weeks, things
have picked up,
a lot,
and I'll talk
more about that
next episode. But
yeah, so a
turbulent, time
coming to where
we are now,
but so much
learning and I,
I wouldn't change
it at all.
yeah, things are
always more
bumpy than we
expect, I think,
and we learn
our best lessons
just going out
and trying and
doing it. So
yeah, super excited
to share more
of this
journey with
you guys and
talk about it,
and talk about
the day-to-day.
thanks for
all the support
that has
come through
yeah, excited to
keep you
into this.